Hannah McDonald

0478 961 223

Email: hannahgmacca@gmail.com
GitHub: https://github.com/hannahgmacca@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-mcdonald-1563aa1a5/

People-orientated front-end developer in training. Exceptional communication and teamwork skills developed from 6+ years of working in retail. Holds a unique set of interpersonal and technical abilities. Seeking an internship position in development that will support my growth as a front-end developer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lismore McDonalds

Front-counter worker Feb 2014- Jan 2015

- Built a strong foundation for work ethics and practices.
- Time management and communication skills allowed me to excel in the most high-pressure situations.
- Ability to overcome any unpleasant customer situations with resilience and good attitude.

Network Video Lismore

Shift supervisor Jan 2015- Mar 2020

- Attention to detail required when handling financial responsibilities and stock management.
- Advanced teamwork and leadership skills was shown at this job as training and supervising was key responsibility.
- Unique interpersonal abilities required as small customer base relied on building a strong rapport to ensure sales were met.

Coles Mermaid Waters

Service supervisor Mar 2020 - Sep 2020

- Began as register attendant during peak of COVID19 before then becoming a supervisor.
- Supervising service operations through managing front end staff
- Customer interactions involve solving complaints, enquires and other general retail services.

SOS Phone Repairs Coolangatta

Lead technician / Manager Sep 2020 – present

- Interact with customers to understand their problem
- Replace phone components such as battery, screens and small parts
- Troubleshoot software and hardware issues through research and communication with team-members

PERSONALITY AND ATTRIBUTES

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.
- Keen desire to learn allows me to develop new skills quickly.
- Seeks mentorship and guidance when needed.
- Thrives in situations that rely on teamwork and peer support.
- Seeks to approach difficult challenges with both a creative and logical mindset.

EDUCATION

Southern Cross University

BA of IT (incomplete) 2019-2020

- Major: User Experience Design
- Notable coursework completed: Programming 1, Programming 2, Web Development 1, Cyber Security, Systems Analysis & Design, Database Systems, Resources for User Interaction GPA: 6.42

Coder Academy

Diploma of IT 2020 - 2021

- Major: Full-stack website development
- Notable coursework completed:

TECHNICAL ABILITIES

(See GitHub for projects)

- HTML/CSS
- Java
- SQL

ACHIEVEMENTS & ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

- SCU Women In Tech Award for Excellence
- SCU Chancellors Academia Award
- Developing a presentation with a female workshop group to be delivered at a Brisbane Tech Newbies meet up
- Member of multiple tech meet-up groups (Brisbane Tech Newbies, Women in Agile)
- Coder Academy Diversity Scholarship recipient

REFERENCES

KRIS LANARCH

Previous employer 6622 1000 Store@networkvideolismore.com.au Network Video Manager

JENNIFER DOHERTY

Mentor 0405 248 019 dohertyja@gmail.com Cupid Media Project Manager